Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Trade Divisions and Conferences records 1942-2003 IBT0013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Bakery Conference Proceedings, 1942-1973; Series 3; 1 Linear Feet
  - Proceedings, 1970 August 18-20; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings, 1971 August 11-13; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings, 1972 August 21-23; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings, 1973 August 20-22; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- National Warehouse Division, 1948-1981; Series 4; 1 Linear Feet
  Biographical / Historical
  The IBT Warehouse Division provides a variety of support services to Teamsters local unions representing members employed in warehousing, distribution, food processing and related industries. This includes job classifications such as drivers, lift truck operators, equipment operators, food processing workers and clerical workers. The Division was formed in September 1948 at a conference held in Chicago that drew close to 300 attendees. The Warehouse Division assists local unions in designing and executing successful bargaining and campaign strategies. It is also responsible for conducting production standards reports and time studies.
  The Materials of this series include proceedings and annual reports. They range from 1948 to 1981, and represent the history of the National Warehouse Conferences of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. The early proceedings contain transcripts of the meetings while the later proceedings contain the remarks of various speakers, sometimes only in part. The annual reports (from 1954-1957) contain summaries of the year's activities, along with lists of various officers and committee members.
  - Proceedings, 1948 September 16-17; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1954 April -1955 April; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1955-1956; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1956-1957; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings, 1973 July 23-26; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings, 1974 August 12-15; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings, 1975 August 11-14; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings, 1977 June 26-30; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings, 1978 August 13-17; Series 4 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, 1979 July 15-19; Series 4 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings, 1981 January 4-8; Series 4 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Warehouse Division, 2001 Convention Pin, IBT 0013 Series 4 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 9)
- Industrial Trade Division Conference, 2007-2015; Series 5
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  This series contains files from the IBT Industrial Trade Divisions Conference.
  - Teamsters Directory, 2007-2008 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Trade Divisions Conference Evaluation Forms, 2015 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Trade Divisions Conference Brochures, Undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Trade Division Pin, IBT 0013 Series 5 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 10)
- Other Divisions, IBT 0013 Series 6
  - Teamster Rod and Gun Club Badge, 1948; IBT 0013 Series 6 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper, Magazine and Electronic Media Division Lapel Pin, ND, IBT0013, Series 6 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Construction Division Pin, IBT 0013 Series 6 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Port Division Pin, IBT 0013 Series 6 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Redi-Mix Division Pin, IBT0013 Series 6 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Solid Waste Division Pin, IBT0013 Series 6 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Tankhaul Division Pin, IBT0013 Series 6 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 15)